They're not 21 anymore.
22 Jump Street is a crime, comedy, action film directed by Phil Lord.
After making their way through high school (twice), big changes are in store for
officers Schmidt and Jenko when they go deep undercover at a local college.
But when Jenko meets a kindred spirit on the football team, and Schmidt infiltrates
the bohemian art major scene, they begin to question their partnership.
Now they don't have to just crack the case - they have to
figure out if they can have a mature relationship.
If these two overgrown adolescents can grow from freshmen into real men,
college might be the best thing that ever happened to them.
Schmidt, played by Jonah Hill.
Jenko, played by Channing Tatum.
The Ghost, played by Peter Stormare.
Zook, played by Wyatt Russell.
Maya, played by Amber Stevens West.
Mercedes, played by Jillian Bell.
22 Jump Street is a 2014 American buddy cop action comedy film directed by Phil Lord and Christopher Miller, written by
Jonah Hill, Michael Bacall, Oren Uziel and Rodney Rothman and produced by and starring Hill and Channing Tatum.
Ice Cube and Peter Stormare also star.
It is the sequel to the 2012 film 21 Jump Street, which is
based on the television series of the same name.
The plot follows police officers Schmidt and Jenko as they go undercover
at a college in order to find the supplier of a new drug.
Plans for a Jump Street sequel began the week of the first film's release.
Hill and Tatum were quickly confirmed to be reprising their roles, while Miller
and Lord announced they'd be returning to direct in July 2013.
Filming took place from September to December of that same year in New
Orleans, Louisiana, as well as San Juan, Puerto Rico.
22 Jump Street premiered on June 4, 2014, in New York City, and was theatrically released in
the United States on June 13 by Columbia Pictures and Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (MGM).
It received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $331 million worldwide.
A third film, as well as a female-led spin-off and a possible crossover with the
Men in Black franchise, were discussed but never came to fruition.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, sarcasm,
college, male friendship, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.